syl.com 2012-10-02

# Free online dating service SearchYourLove

SYL.com is committed to protect the privacy rights of our users at all times. Any and all the information collected on this site will be kept with the utmost care and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. If you have any questions, please feel free to call or email us. 

## About Us

SYL.com is a free social network for online communicating available to any person meeting age criteria. 

## Required Information

In the online registration form you are asked to provide certain personal information such as name, e-mail address, sex, date of birth, and location. You can also provide optional details about yourself. Your personal information is available to you at all times, and you can change, modify, update or delete it. 

We require a valid e-mail address because we might need to use it for communication purposes. 

It is up to you to post additional information about yourself, name your occupation, education, beliefs, family information, marital status and children. 

You cannot post any personal contact information in your profile for whatever reason. 

We expressly state that we retain the right to cancel the accounts and delete profiles of the users who violate our terms and services and misuse our services. 

## IP Addresses and Cookies

Certain information, such as your IP address, is automatically tracked by our servers while you are using our web site. 

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies. A session ID cookie simply terminates once a user closes the browser. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. 

## Use of Information

We use the information of our users for statistical purposes, analyze it in order to target our marketing efforts better, to process payments, to work on further improvement of our web site in order to better serve your online needs. Whatever purpose of the use is, it is most certainly ethical and lawful at all times. 

We may user your personal profile information in order to communicate with you by sending notifications that may be of interest to you and/or descriptions and promotions of our new services and offers. You can opt in or out for these notifications. 

## Disclosure of Information

We disclose the information to our affiliates, partners and subsidiary companies. We make all reasonable efforts to make sure that whatever we disclose the information for, it is used only for ethical and lawful purposes. 

We expressly state that we retain the right to disclose your information if required by law when the disclosure is necessary to protect our rights. 

## Your Feedback

We greatly appreciate your feedback. It is very important for us to know what you think about our services, and we always try to take into account all suggestions and criticism. The words of appreciation that we receive from our users make our work worthwhile. We strongly encourage you send us your opinions regarding our services at all times, and we retain a right to publish them along with the name (or initials) and geographic location provided in the email, unless you ask us not to do so. If you do not wish your feedback to be published for any reason, please state so in your message. 

## Your Consent

By using our site, you give us your permission to collect and use your personal information as stated in this Privacy Statement. 

## Age Requirements

We specifically state that our users should be at least 18 years of age. We do not encourage children or minors to use our services, we do not knowingly market our services to them and we take all reasonable efforts to prevent underage Internet users from using our web site services. 

## Your Use of Information

You may not use the information about other users for any commercial purposes, for sending spam, for harassing them and making them treats of any kind. We cancel the accounts and delete the personal information of those who misuse the information about our users. 

## Your Unread Messages

We expressly state that if you do not log in and do not use our service for an extended period of time, we retain the right to send you a notification and/or delete the unread messages from our servers. 

## Your Password

We do not disclose your password, ever, to anyone, under any circumstances, and we assume no responsibility if, having lost control over your password, you allowed someone to change your personal information on your behalf or use your profile to access our services. 

## Changing Your Personal Information

You can review and change your personal information at any time. 

## Data Protection

We take all reasonable efforts to prevent your information from loss, misuse and/or alteration and protect your confidentiality and privacy. We cannot guarantee 100% security of information, because nobody on the Internet can; however, we work every day to make sure that your data is secure and you use our services without being subjected to disclosure. 

## This Privacy Statement

We reserve the right to make changes to our privacy policy and this privacy statement at any time for whatever reason. We do not notify our users of any changes personally, so we encourage you to check the privacy statement from time to time. The significant changes to this privacy statement, if we ever make any, will be described on the home page of our web site.
